Narrator: 1
GPS: In 100 feet, turn left. Turn left.
Lisa: Don’t turn right! Turn left!
Mel: It’s right, I’m sure.
Lisa: No, it isn’t.
Mel: Yes, it is!
Lisa: No, it isn’t!
This is wrong!
Narrator: 2
Lisa: I’m thirsty. Where’s the water?
Mel: Sorry, it’s empty.
Lisa: Empty?
Mel: Yes, empty.
I’m hungry. And Alfie’s hungry.
Let’s stop at a café.
Lisa: OK, good idea.
Narrator: 3
Mel: Brrrr…
Lisa: What’s the matter?
Mel: I’m cold.
Can you close your window?
Lisa: I’m not cold! I’m hot!
Mel: Well, I’m cold. And Alfie’s cold.
Lisa: OK.
Mel: And please don’t drive fast!
It’s really dangerous.
Lisa: It’s fine. Don’t worry!
Mel: Be careful!
Narrator: 4
Lisa: It’s late. Let’s look for a hotel.
Mel: Oh, let’s not stop now.
Lisa: I’m tired and it’s dark.
And Alfie’s tired, too.
Mel: OK, OK.
Look for a hotel near here.
Lisa: The Highland Hotel’s 20 miles from here.
Mel: Fine. No problem.
Let’s go there.